<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building A Mechanical Keyboard</title>
      <link>https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/building-a-mechanical-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/building-a-mechanical-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>Background I&amp;rsquo;ve been using a Coolermaster TKL layout mechanical keyboard with Cherry MX Blue switches (the loud tactile clicky ones) for quite a while now, but I was recently inspired by Taeha Types and Andy V Nguyen on YouTube to look into building my own mechanical keyboard. I went down the rabbithole and decided to document the experience here.
Taeha Types has a great starting point video explaining everything that goes into a mechanical keyboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laziness and Streams - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/laziness-and-streams-pt-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/laziness-and-streams-pt-2/</guid>
      <description>Following up from Laziness and Streams - Part 1 and inspired by Jeremy Fairbank&amp;rsquo;s function streams in JavaScript I wanted to try to implement a lazy Stream in Python. The problem is that Python does not have non-strict arguments like Scala does with the =&amp;gt; operator. Python does have a lambda keyword which you can use to define functions in a single line expression. The lambda keyword doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to take arguments, so it can be used as a non-strictness operator hack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laziness and Streams - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/laziness-and-streams-pt-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jjmalina.github.io/posts/laziness-and-streams-pt-1/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m currently working my way through Functional Programming in Scala. Chapter 5 focuses on non-strictness as a property of functions. I found the chapter really fascinating because this property allows one to build a lazily evaluated list. In the next post, I&amp;rsquo;ll try doing the same in Python. What follows here my explanation in Scala taken from the book. I try to cover the Scala specific syntax and features so hopefully this makes sense even if you&amp;rsquo;re not familiar with Scala.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
